[rock music playing]
CHAPTER 1:
I AM A WEB NOVEL WRITER
[Western standoff music playing]
[person 1] Ho has been friends
with Yeon-hui since childhood.
HO
BITTERSWEET HEART
He seems taciturn and nonchalant,
but he's unexpectedly caring,
that's his charm point.
Jin is a college friend of Yeon-hui's.
JIN
RAY OF SUNSHINE
He's so sweet you'd think he's an angel.
Fans are split
between those who support
the Yeon-hui and Ho couple…
and those who support
the Yeon-hui and Jin couple. YeonJin.
But I…
[whimsical music playing]
Didn't I tell you to stay out of my sight?
Every time I see you,
I get so damn irritated.
Why?
Why the hell?
[music stops]
Why the hell couldn't I have
met you sooner?
[person 1] …I'm Team HoJin.
-[romantic music playing]
-You fool.
[person 1] They have no choice
but to hide their feelings.
Look at the way they look at each other.
[phone ringing]
Sorry.
Hello, Dad.
What was that?
[Dad] I'm getting remarried.
To Geum-yeong.
You and Ho will be brothers. [laughs]
You better keep getting along
with each other. [laughs]
[exhales sharply]
-Hold up, hold up.
-[bell rings]
I just can't let
something like this slide.
Are you out of your mind?
Hey! I'm talking to you!
Me?
This is the last episode.
Isn't that right?
-It is.
-And you're gonna ruin it like that?
I've been patient this whole time,
but the story is way too slow.
They don't even realize
they like each other
until the last episode?
That makes no sense.
What's with the random
"they're brothers" twist?
Are you kidding me?
Well, there might be a second season.
[scoffs] Really?
After that mess you wrote,
you're hoping for a second season?
You just caused all this,
and no one wants to read your stuff!
[gasps]
That's so harsh.
Is that her?
The writer who
totally butchered everything,
from characters to narratives,
plots, and plausibility?
[stammers]
[sirens wailing]
Huh?
[officer] Where is she?
-Over there.
-Arrest her.
Hmm?
Freeze! Hands off the keyboard!
Don't touch it!
-[stammers] What…
-I said freeze!
B-But I didn't do anything at all.
Oh, come on. You already know
your writing sucks.
[stutters] Writing a bad novel…
i-isn't a crime, you know!
-Oh, yes it is!
-[whimpers]
Under Article 1, Clause 1
of the Web Novel Act,
-bad writers must be punished.
-What?
-Therefore, Yeo Eui-ju…
-Huh? What?
-…you're under arrest.
-Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh!
Don't do this! Don't do this!
Don't do this!
[gasps, breathes sharply]
[sighs, grunts]
[sighs, sniffles]
[groans]
I really thought I was getting arrested.
[sighs]
[shudders, sniffles]
PAZER WEB NOVEL PORTAL
[sniffles]
[sighs]
I am…
PAZER WEB NOVEL PORTAL
…a writer.
[sighs]
A writer who specializes in…
BL.
BL: ABBREVIATION OF BOYS' LOVE
PRIZE
WRITING CONTEST
My pen name
is Imuk.
No one reads my stuff.
THEY CAME TOGETHER
No one but me.
The one with two views was just
someone who clicked by accident.
They could've at least left
a hate comment while they were at it.
ZERO REVIEWS
[sniffles]
This is Yeo Eui-do.
He's the only brat
who knows that I write BL novels.
Cola.
YEO EUI-DO
COKE ADDICT BROTHER
He's been blackmailing me with that.
EPISODE 1
[sighs]
What should I write for my next piece?
[groans]
I can't afford another big failure.
[romantic music playing]
[person 1 groans]
Aren't your legs sore? They feel tense.
[person 2] Did you shower?
You smell really nice.
Is that the one I got you?
[person 1] Ooh, you're way too tense. Huh?
You need more stretching.
[person 1, person 3 groaning]
[person 1] Stand up.
Let's loosen up your shoulders.
[person 3] Hey, no, not here!
[person 1] Ugh, let's do it inside, then.
[person 3 stammering] What, no, stop!
Jung, come on, it's still too early!
[person 2] Did you have a good night?
I couldn't sleep one bit because of you.
Because you weren't with me.
So tonight,
-I don't want to sleep alone.
[chuckles]
Huh?
[person 2] What's with that girl?
Is she here for me?
Wasn't that a boy?
-It was a girl.
-I see.
-How are your eyes?
-They're okay.
What's wrong with Dong-ju?
-He got a cramp.
-Why did Gi-jeon carry him in?
He says it's for training.
[door opens]
CHAPTER 2: DO YOU KNOW
WHY STUDENTS WEAR UNIFORMS?
EUI-JU'S HOUSE - SHIN,
YOON-JU, EUI-JU, EUI-DO, SUNI
Ma, did the twins and their family
who used to live at the big white house
move away?
Did they?
Well, it looks like someone else moved in.
It's just a bunch of guys now.
Really?
I heard the twins' dad got promoted.
Maybe that's why they moved.
Well, he should've said goodbye.
What about us? When can we move?
Isn't it nice here?
I turned down a promotion, huh?
[chuckles]
-That's right. Eat up.
-[Eui-ju chuckles]
[whispers] Pervert!
I think I'm done eating.
Come on, eat some more.
[Eui-ju] It's okay. I'll run late if I do.
I'm off to school now.
-[Ma] Bye! Be safe!
-[Shin] Careful on the road.
I said I'd go by myself.
Ah, come on, just listen to me.
Let's go together.
That car air freshener smells awful.
No, wait a second.
I'm going with you.
Forget it. Stay out of my business.
What on earth?
Aren't they the guys from yesterday?
Hey, Woo-su!
I can't do that.
-You know I can't do that.
-That's enough!
Oh, this is crazy.
It's a hassle.
[gasps] Couple fight?
Please listen to me.
How long do I have to listen to you for?
Let's just take the car and make it easy.
I don't wanna keep doing what you want.
I'm saying I'll go alone.
Ugh, that one's just a big jerk.
[clicks tongue]
The others are almost ready.
Just give them a minute.
Treating someone nice like that,
he's just gonna regret it.
-[chuckles]
-[mosquito buzzing]
Ouch.
Knock it off already.
-Woo-su!
-Did it get on my face?
[sighs]
Hold on a second.
[Eui-ju] Whoa. He's gorgeous!
Were you filming?
-What?
-I saw you filming us. Delete it.
[stammers, sighs] No, I didn't.
I was seeing if I got a bug on my face.
[scoffs]
Listen I'm not some kind of creep
who secretly films people on the street.
I'll let it slide if you delete it,
all right? So choose carefully.
I said that I didn't do it.
-What's wrong?
-She was filming us.
I bet she wants to post it
just to get comments.
ZERO COMMENTS
Just for comments?
I do want comments!
The more, the better.
I completely wrecked the ending.
And I still… I still didn't even get
a single hate comment.
Do you have any idea
how humiliating that is?
A hundred episodes and nothing.
-Oh, darn.
-Don't change the subject.
That's enough.
You really weren't filming?
Mm-hmm.
She said she wasn't.
But I saw you, you were hiding
right there, filming us.
[scoffs]
-Give it to me, I'm checking.
-Oh, hey! What the heck?
-What are you doing? Let go.
-Let go.
-Come on, let go of it.
-Stop. Stop it.
I didn't film anything. I didn't! [grunts]
[exclaims]
[gasps]
[whimpering] No. No, no, no.
No, please, no. Please, please.
[gasps]
Oh, no.
[crying]
You broke my phone! Are you serious?
What are you gonna do about this?
I can't believe this!
You should've just let me
check your phone.
[Dong-ju] Sorry about this, kid.
He was overreacting
because he has past trauma
from getting filmed
without his permission.
We'll compensate you
for your broken phone.
[breathing deeply]
Forget it! Geez.
You know why students wear uniforms?
It's a way of identifying them.
You better not spread
what you filmed today,
or I'll teach you what it means
to regret doing something.
Such an asshole!
Hey!
Why are you still here?
We're running late. Come with us.
Oh, wait. Wait a second.
[K-pop music playing]
Slow down.
JEONJU MURIM GIRLS' HIGH
CHAPTER 3:
SO, THAT ASSHOLE IS MY…
[music continues]
-Eui-ju! Yeo Eui-ju!
-Oh. [chuckles]
[Eui-ju] This is my bestie, Choi Go-ya.
She's an art talent,
and she's always had a boyfriend,
ever since we were in sixth grade.
I feel like I've gained at least 4 pounds
after all that sleeping and eating.
[sighs]
What the… What happened?
This guy recently moved
into my neighborhood,
and he thought I was filming him,
so he wanted to check my phone.
I didn't let him take it
and this happened.
Dang.
And you let him get away with it?
You should've demanded compensation
or got his number
to make him pay the hard way!
No. I didn't want to.
-He looked like he had a nasty temper.
-[phone buzzing]
[sighs]
What? Who is that?
My ex.
You broke up again?
Didn't you say he was the most
handsome guy at your academy?
I wonder when I'll get to meet
my one true love.
Lucky you.
I haven't even had my first love yet.
[sighs]
Maybe my novels are boring
because I've never been in a relationship.
Not true…
Dating may help, but then…
[groans] …it ruins your fantasies
the more you date.
In your case you're better off writing,
because you still fantasize
about dating and romance.
You think?
Hmm. What is it?
Do you have writer's block?
You said you finished.
I did. I finished it.
When are you going to let me read them?
You didn't tell me the titles
or your pen name.
That's just too mean.
I told you already.
I'm taking it to my grave.
[chuckles] If it's a mega hit,
are you going to keep it a secret then?
Mega hit?
Aw, you'll be the first
to hear the news, then.
[both laughing]
I really hope it comes true. A mega hit.
[students chattering]
[student 1] What are you guys looking at?
[student 2] Go-ya! Eui-ju!
-Hey, Eui-ju. Eui-ju, over here.
-Over here! Hurry!
-Come on. Hurry!
-What's going on? I wanna know. Tell me.
[clamoring]
[student 3] Do you see them?
Aw, they've finally come,
after all those rumors.
-[student 2] Wow. [sighing]
-Dang, all the new teachers are men.
But they're not just men.
They're drop-dead gorgeous men.
Oh, this is seriously insane.
Look, they're a solid ten,
a whole package. [sighs]
I'm going crazy here. I'm going crazy.
I can't handle it.
I've never wanted to enter
the teachers' office this much
in my whole life. [moans]
[student 2] Young-hee said we were
not allowed in and locked the doors.
Why wouldn't she let the students watch
the new teachers
-introduce themselves?
-[student 3] I know.
That's Jung Gi-jeon.
JUNG GI-JEON
He's a PE teacher.
He used to be a national athlete.
He was the first Korean to place fourth
in the luge at the Winter Games.
Oh, dang. Look at him. [gasps] Wow.
That's Noh Da-ju. He's multilingual.
He's gonna teach Japanese
and first-grade Spanish.
[in Spanish] When I was six…
[student 3, in English]
He made a speech at the TUD Talk
titled Secret to Conquering
Foreign Languages.
And rumor says he's the youngest son
of a filthy-rich family.
I'm so glad I'm here today.
[student 3] Oh. That's Yoon Dong-ju,
a Korean literature teacher.
What's that poem he published through
Literary Youth in 2020? "My Mother"?
I found him.
My true love.
Hold on a second.
He's a Korean literature teacher?
[gasps] There's no way.
It can't be.
This is Ga Woo-su. Our new math teacher.
So. Thanks to his outstanding
research accomplishments in college,
he was offered positions
by several Ivy League universities
but he decided to join us here.
-[stammers]
-["Symphony No. 5 in C Minor" playing]
[Eui-ju] Isn't he that jerk?
He's a Mensa member.
-You heard her, right?
-[staff applauding]
He's a Mensa member.
So in a few words, he's a math genius.
[staff cheering, applauding]
[students clamoring]
[screaming]
[music continues]
[all exclaim]
[no audible dialogue]
Sorry, I dropped my phone.
[chuckles] Sorry.
[music ends]
Oh, my goodness. Did you guys see them?
I'm going for Da-ju.
He's my one and only pick.
The era of Ha E-den is long gone now.
Hey, don't you compare him to them, girl.
We've adored him only because he's cute.
[laughs]
Were you talking about me?
This early in the day?
HA E-DEN
MUSIC TEACHER
-[chuckles]
-[chuckles] No, we weren't.
[scoffs] Go-ya. How cold.
You hurt my feelings.
Thank you for filling in for
our homeroom teacher.
[all] Thank you very much.
-What the--
-[student 3 chuckles]
-Good morning.
-What on earth…
-No, it's not good.
-Good morning.
-Have they lost their minds altogether?
[students chattering]
MURIM GIRL'S HIGH
11TH GRADE CLASS 2
I'm going to wear full makeup
every day from now on.
Who's your favorite one?
Mr. Dong-ju. [laughs]
-He's my husband.
-[both laughing]
What should I major in
to become a devoted wife?
Mr. Yoon seems to prefer
a docile type, though.
My-My pick is the Japanese teacher, okay?
Go back to what you were doing.
There, there.
-Who did you pick?
-For what?
Your crush? That's what I meant.
We shouldn't overlap.
Whatever, I don't care
about choosing a crush.
But Mr. Yoon isn't your type, though.
-I changed.
-Mmm.
-[both chuckle]
-Wait. Uh, uh. Hold on.
-I just got goose bumps.
-Why? What is it?
Wait, listen,
this means one of them… [gasps]
…is going to be our homeroom teacher.
-[squealing] Sweet!
-[squealing] This is insane!
[student 4] Shut up!
EUN HA-SU
TOP OF THE SCHOOL, PRESENCE
Keep it down, will you?
[clears throat]
Class hasn't started yet.
Yes, but at least don't disturb others.
[softly] As if she owns this class.
You're low on sugar, aren't you?
How about a cafeteria run?
Where are you going?
[K-pop music playing]
BRACKET BY SPORT
KOREAN LITERATURE TIMETABLE
MR. GA WOO-SU
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH
11TH GRADE TEACHERS' OFFICE
[music continues]
[camera shutter clicking]
KOREAN LITERATURE TIMETABLE
Dong-ju, are you coloring right now?
Oh. [chuckles]
I won't get confused this way.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Feeling okay?
Do you need anything?
No, thanks.
I should be getting better soon.
Darn it.
[sighs]
Did you come here to clean?
Knock it off.
Leave me alone.
[sighs] In this jungle-like society,
standing out means death.
You're just a clueless kid who
doesn't understand how the world works.
-Let's change desks. I can't stand him.
-Oh, please.
I'd love to stay here in front of you.
I miss you even when I'm seeing you.
Just settle for it. It's been decided.
-I don't want to face this bat every day.
-What?
I told you not to call me that.
I hate hearing that word.
It's like "Voldemort" to me,
you understand?
Don't you know it disgusts me? Mm-mm-mmm.
Oh, yes, you do. There's no freaking way
that the genius Ga Woo-su
wouldn't remember it.
My hippocampus is not like yours.
It not only takes part
in learning and memory,
but also in emotional control,
which is why I can't stand facing you.
No. No, no, no.
Don't humiliate me.
You memory freak!
Hey, fruit bat!
What? You four-eyed nerd?
-Four-eyed nerd?
-Darn you…
[Dong-ju] That's enough already.
[intercom beeping]
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
Hmm. [sighs] How can you be sure
that Mr. Yoon is your true love?
You've only just met him.
Hmm.
Love is like…
first snow. Right in that moment,
when you see them,
oh, you just have this feeling.
And you know they're the one.
And it always comes
when you least expect it.
So then, does that mean
that all your countless ex-boyfriends
weren't your first snow, Choi Go-ya?
I thought they were,
but they turned out to be frost.
[chuckles]
My first snow actually came today.
And when will I get my first snow, then?
I told you.
It comes when you least expect it to.
It hits you
out of nowhere
-before you can react. Bam!
-[student] Thank you.
-Ouch!
-[cashier] No problem. See you.
[laughs]
-How much is it?
-One thirty-three.
-[both] Thank you.
-No problem.
Lucky you.
While one new teacher
has become your first snow,
I got involved with another
in a messed-up way.
-[Go-ya laughs]
-Ugh, whatever.
[sighs] Well.
Come to think of it, this must be why
he mentioned school uniforms and stuff.
[scoffs]
So what if he's a genius?
He has a shitty personality. Ugh.
[romantic music playing]
-[Go-ya] What is it?
-[music stops]
[whimpering]
[door creaking]
[romantic music resumes]
[music stops]
[rock music playing]
NO WAY
I'M YOUR HOMEROOM TEACHER
[exhales sharply]